Pouya **Aghahoseini**

COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENT · AMIRKABIR UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

No.16, Tavakol Alley, 17-Shahrivar Ave, Tehran, 1153963716, Iran

🛮 (+98) 9102117201 | 🚾 pouyaaghahoseini@gmail.com | 🌴 pouyaaghahoseini.github.io | 🖸 pouyaaghahoseini | 🛅 pouyaaghahoseini

Summary_

Currently studying Computer Science at Amirkabir University of Technology. Adept to code in C/C++, Python, and MySQL and also familiar with numPy and Pandas Libraries. During my recent years in Amirkabir, I have had the opportunity to gain lots of teamwork experiences, through course projects and more significantly, through extracurricular activities in student scientific chapter.

Skills

Programming C/C++, Python, R, MATLAB

Web Technologies HTML, CSS, Javascript, MySQL

Libraries numPy, Pandas

Operating Systems Linux, Windows

Languages Persian, English(Proficient)

Miscellaneous MTFX, Jupyter, Git, Microsoft Office, GAMS(Optimization), Database Design

Education_

Amirkabir University of Technology

_

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE

Major in Computer Science, CGPA: 17.28/20

Allameh Helli High School
DIPLOMA IN MATHEMATICS AND PHYSICS

• Grade: 18.5/20

Experience

Math & Computer Science Faculty, Amirkabir University of Technology

Tehran, Iran Sep 2018 - Present

Tehran Iran

2016 - Present

Tehran, Iran

2012 - 2016

TEACHING ASSISTANT

- Design and Analysis of Algorithms
- Data Structures and Algorithms
- Fundamentals of Programming: C Language
- · Compilers
- Introduction to the Theory of Computation

Student Scientific Chapter, Amirkabir University of Technology

Tehran, Iran Mar. 2018 - Mar. 2019

HEAD OF INFORMATICS AND COMPETITIONS

- Organized Data Science Seminars And Workshops.
- · Coordinated 5 ACM Contests.
- Arranged On-Site Visits To Leading Tech Companies In Tehran.
- Arranged Talks With Alumni Currently Studying Or Working Abroad.
- Held 2018 New Student Orientation Program.
- Organized And Instructed Exam Preparation Classes(Calculus, Programming, Differential Equations).

11th Winter School on Computational Geometry, Amirkabir University of Technology

Tehran, Iran

ORGANIZING COMMITTEE MEMBER

March 2019

- The Winter School on Computational Geometry is held every year by Math and Computer Science Faculty, in collaboration with IPM Institute for Research in Fundamental Sciences.
- Notable researchers in computational geometry are invited for seminars and workshops in this program.

Projects

Medify: An Application for Fixing Tags And Organizing Media Files

Amirkabir University of Technology

Software Design Course | 4 member team | 🧿 Github

Jan. 2018 - Jul. 2018

- The application was Developed using ${\bf Scrum\ Methodology}$ for Agile Software Development.
- We did 5 presentations throughout including a 5-minute startup pitch presentation and the presentation of the first MVP

FEBRUARY 16, 2020 POUYA AGHAHOSEINI · RÉSUMÉ

Designing and Creating A Database From YAGO Datasets

DATABASE COURSE PROJECT ☐ GITHUB

- Data Extraction using TSV files acquired from max plank institute website.
- Processing and Clustering TSV files with Python and MySQL.
- Designing and Creating A 3NF Database.

Factory Simulation with MATLAB

SIMULATION PROJECT O GITHUB

- System modeling and simulation with MATLAB
- Simulation of a factory with different performances and various response time of each agent.

Amirkabir University of Technology

Jan. 2018 - Jul. 2018

Amirkabir University of Technology

Sep. 2018 - Jan. 2019